<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Sinclair Huang - Research &amp; Consulting</title>
    <link>https://sinclairhuang.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sinclair Huang - Research &amp; Consulting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.123.7</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sinclairhuang.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Research Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://sinclairhuang.org/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sinclairhuang.org/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my professional research website. This platform showcases my academic work, publications, and ongoing research projects.
Current Focus I am currently working on several research initiatives:
AI Semiconductor Valuation - Comprehensive analysis using GEE regression and Random Forest methodologies Precision Oncology - Exploring AlphaFold 3 applications in drug discovery Carbon Black Industry - Strategic optimization for high-value applications Stay tuned for updates on publications and research findings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaFold 3 and the Future of Drug Discovery</title>
      <link>https://sinclairhuang.org/blog/thoughts/2024-12-first-thought/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sinclairhuang.org/blog/thoughts/2024-12-first-thought/</guid>
      <description>Quick thoughts on how AlphaFold 3 is transforming molecular medicine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Title</title>
      <link>https://sinclairhuang.org/blog/thoughts/yyyy-mm-dd-title/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sinclairhuang.org/blog/thoughts/yyyy-mm-dd-title/</guid>
      <description>Your content here&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sinclairhuang.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sinclairhuang.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Sinclair Huang Executive Doctorate of Business Administration (EDBA), HEC Liège
Special Advisor to the Chairman, Continental Carbon Co., Ltd.
Professional Background With over 30 years of cross-industry experience spanning Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s electronics, biotechnology, and chemical industries, I bring a unique blend of technical expertise and strategic insight to address complex business challenges.
Research Focus My research centers on three core areas:
AI Semiconductors: Quantitative valuation analysis of 95 global AI semiconductor companies, examining market positioning, technological capabilities, and competitive dynamics in the rapidly evolving AI chip landscape Precision Oncology: Exploring AlphaFold 3 applications in drug discovery, focusing on how protein structure prediction advances therapeutic development and personalized cancer treatment approaches Industry Optimization: Carbon black manufacturing optimization through process innovation and operational excellence Current Work As Special Advisor to the Chairman at Continental Carbon Co.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consulting Services</title>
      <link>https://sinclairhuang.org/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sinclairhuang.org/consulting/</guid>
      <description>Strategic advisory in AI, biotechnology, and competitive intelligence</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
